jgwentworth.com 2015-03-15

# Privacy Policy - J.G. WentworthJ.G. Wentworth

This Privacy Policy is provided by J.G. Wentworth (“the Company”), on behalf of itself and certain of the various companies that it owns.

Your privacy is important to us.  In this Privacy Policy, we explain what personal information we collect, and how we protect it.

In Section I, the Company provides a Financial Privacy Statement.  This Financial Privacy Statement applies to all customer information we obtain.

In Section II, the Company explains some Additional Protections for Confidential Health and Medical Information.

Some members of the Company PT may collect confidential health and medical information in connection with requested transactions. If you are asked for non-public personal health information, you will be provided a separate disclosure explaining how that information will be protected and used.

In Section III, the Company provides a Website Privacy Statement, which describes the information we collect when you visit or use our website.

Lastly, in Section IV, we list the companies to which this Privacy Policy applies.

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, or if you wish to correct any information that you have previously provided, please contact us at:

Customer Service—Privacy Coordinator – Legal Department

J.G. Wentworth  
201 King of Prussia Road  
Radnor, PA 19087  
1 (800) 715-8127

The date of this policy is August 15, 2013.

**SECTION I:   FINANCIAL PRIVACY STATEMENT**

**Why is this notice provided?  **

Companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.  Please note that additional protections apply to confidential health and medical information submitted.  These additional protections are described in separate disclosures to be provided at the time of collection.  See Section II, below.

**What types of personal information do you collect and share?  **

The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the transaction(s) you have with us. This information can include:

  * Social Security number;
  * Structured settlement balances;
  * Transaction history;
  * Contact information (e.g.:  name, address, telephone number(s), email);
  * Credit history;
  * Information contained in public records;
  * Or any other information and documents you provide to us or authorize us to obtain.

**How will my personal information be shared?  **

Most companies need to share personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons the Company can share your personal information; the reasons the Company chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.

**Reasons We Can Share Your Personal Information** | **Does** the **** Company **Reserve The Right To Share?** | **Can You Limit This Sharing?**  
---|---|---  
**For our everyday business purposes—** such as to process your transactions with us or our Affiliates, to fund or audit your transactions, to maintain/service your transaction(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus ****|  Yes | No  
**For our marketing purposes—** to offer our transactions to you ****|  Yes | No  
**For joint marketing with other companies** | Yes | No  
**Reasons We Can Share Your Personal Information (continued)** | **Does** the **** Company **Reserve The Right To Share?** | **Can You Limit This Sharing?**  
**For our Affiliates’ everyday business purposes—** information about your transactions and experiences ****|  Yes | No  
**For our Affiliates’ everyday business purposes—** information about your creditworthiness ****|  Yes | Yes  
**For our Affiliates to market to you** | Yes | Yes  
**For Non-affiliates to market to you** | Yes | Yes  
  
Your personal information may also be shared:

  * To establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;
  * In connection with a proposed or actual sale, merger, transfer, exchange or consolidation of any portion of our business;
  * To comply with legal process; or
  * To secure services and advice from our attorneys, accountants and auditors.

**We may also share or disclose your non-public personal information (as described above) with Non-affiliated companies as described below:**

  * As allowed by law, as necessary to effect, process, administer, service or enforce a transaction you have requested.
  * To such firms that perform services on our behalf including, without limitation, auditing, consulting, product administration and marketing.
  * To respond to a subpoena, to prevent fraud, or to comply with an inquiry by a government agency.
  * To such firms that assist us in processing, funding and completing the transaction you have requested and/or who may assist us or attempt to assist us to re-finance or sell/resell the transactions that are completed by us.
  * **Health Information Practices –** We will not share your health information with third parties for marketing purposes without your consent.

**How can I limit the sharing of my information?**

  * Call _1 (800) 715-8127_ —or
  * E-mail us at _Privacy@jgwentworth.com_ and provide contact information

If we have no prior relationship with you, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we send you this notice by mail. When you are no longer our customer, we will continue to share your information as described in this notice. However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.

Direct marketing is email, postal mail and telephone marketing.  Your opt-out choices will last until you cancel them in writing or electronically, subject to applicable law.  Even if you limit direct marketing, we may still contact you to service your transaction or as otherwise allowed by law.

Companies owned by the Company may choose not to share personal information with Affiliates or Non-affiliates, even if that sharing is generally allowed.

**Who is providing this notice?**

This notice is provided by the Company.

**How does the** Company **protect my personal information from unauthorized access and use?**

To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use administrative, physical, and technical security measures. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.

**How does the** Company **collect my personal information?**

We collect your personal information, for example, when you:

  * Request information;
  * Submit an application;
  * Give us your contact information;
  * Or otherwise provide information to us or authorize us to obtain it.

**Why can’t I limit all sharing?**

Federal law gives you the right to limit only:

  * sharing for Affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information about your creditworthiness;
  * Affiliates from using your information to market to you; and
  * sharing for Non-affiliates to market to you.

State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing. ** **

**What happens when I limit information sharing relating to a transaction I completed where there was another individual (e.g. another seller) involved?**

Your choices will apply to all transactions that you have completed where there was with another customer also involved and will apply to their information as well.

**Definitions**

**Affiliates** | Companies related by common ownership or control.  They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.  Our Affiliates include companies that acquire assets such as structured settlement payment streams and lottery payment streams, or offer  other asset-backed transactions.  Every company in  that family is an Affiliate  of every other company in that family.  If you establish a relationship with one company on that list, every other company on that list will be considered an Affiliate.  
---|---  
**Non-affiliates** | Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.   
**Joint marketing** | A formal agreement between Nonaffiliated companies that together market transactions to you. ** **  
  
**Is there anything else I should know?**

**Nevada**.  We are providing you this notice pursuant to state law.  You may be placed on our internal Do Not Call List by following the directions in the section above entitled, “How can I limit the sharing of my information?”.  Nevada law requires that we also provide you with the following contact information: Bureau of Consumer Protection, Office of the Nevada Attorney General, 555 E. Washington St., Suite 3900, Las Vegas, NV 89101; Phone number- 702.486.3132; email: BCPINFO@ag.state.nv.us.  J.G.  Wentworth, 201 King of Prussia Road, Suite 200, Radnor, Pennsylvania 19087; Phone Number:  1 (800) 715-8127 email: Privacy@jgwentworth.com.

**Vermont** :  In accordance with Vermont law, we will not share information we collect about Vermont residents with companies outside of our corporate family, except as permitted by law, such as with your consent, to service  or audit or fund your transactions or with  financial institutions (or other companies) with which we have joint marketing agreements.  We will not share information about your creditworthiness within our corporate family except with your authorization or consent, but we may share information about our transactions or experiences with you within our corporate family without your consent.

**California** :  the Company has a policy of not disclosing personal information of customers to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes if the customer has exercised an option that prevents that information from being disclosed to third parties for those purposes.  You may exercise such an option by following the directions of this Privacy Policy.  In accordance with California law, we will not share information we collect about you with companies outside of the Company, unless the law allows.  For example, we may share information with your consent, to service or audit or fund your transactions, or to provide benefits you are entitled to.  We will limit sharing among our companies to the extent required by California law.

**SECTION II:   Additional Protections for Confidential Health and Medical Information**

We sometimes must collect confidential health and medical information in connection with a transaction you have requested.

If you are asked for confidential health and medical information, you will be provided a separate disclosure explaining in more detail how that information will be protected and used.  That separate disclosure will comply with all applicable legal requirements imposed on the collection of confidential health and medical information.

We do not use or share confidential health and medical information internally or externally, for any purpose except the following:

  * to process your transaction(s);
  * maintain/service your transactions(s);
  * respond to court orders and legal investigations;
  * assisting you in selling an insurance policy;
  * administering any such policy, or claim(s) relating thereto;
  * with non-affiliated funders, investors, lenders or their respective attorneys or other representatives who are assisting us in processing, funding and completing the transaction you have requested and/or who may assist us or attempt to assist us to re-finance or sell/resell the transactions that are completed by us or report to credit bureaus, or
  * as you otherwise authorize via your prior, express, written consent.

We will not share your health information with third parties for marketing purposes without your prior, express, written consent.

**SECTION III:   WEBSITE PRIVACY STATEMENT**

When you visit or browse our website, we and our advertising, marketing, or service partners may collect information such as your Internet Protocol or “IP” address, the “URL” of the web pages you visit, and may use “cookies,” web beacons, or other objects to collect statistical and other information about your use of the our website and other websites.  The purpose of collecting this information is to improve the effectiveness of our website and to conduct targeted advertising or marketing.  The collected information may include, for example, the web pages you visited; the date and time of your visit; the websites you visited immediately before and after visiting our web site; your language preference; demographic information; the kind of browser you use; and the popularity of various advertising words and phrases used by us.  The collection of this information allows for the compilation of aggregate and anonymous information about the usage of our website and other websites.

Furthermore, our website also uses one or more media-players in order to deliver video content.  Accordingly, the site may place a local shared object or “flash cookie” on your computer in order to enhance the functionality of such media-players and to remember personalized settings.

Your web browser should allow you to manage cookies and you can manage your Flash cookies by visiting http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html.  “Flash” is a registered trademark of Adobe Systems Incorporated.

We define children as individuals under the age of 16.   Our website is not intended for the use of children and we do not knowingly solicit or collect information from children.
